playerio.com 2013-11-14

# Player.IO Privacy Policy

This Player.IO Privacy Policy is effective as of May 23, 2013. You can view the prior privacy policy here.

On May 23nd, 2013, Player.IO was acquired by Yahoo! and will soon become a part of the Yahoo! network of products and services. Information collected by Player.IO will continue to be subject to the Player.IO Privacy Policy. In the future, you may be asked to link your current Player.IO information to an existing or new Yahoo! ID. At that point, the Yahoo! Privacy Policy will apply to all information associated with your Player.IO account.

**Player.IO Privacy Policy**

  * Player.IO respects users' personally identifiable information and other data and information we may collect in connection with your use of Player.IO services (for the purposes of this policy, "personal data") and will comply with applicable data protection regulations.
  * Player.IO stores a cookie on the user's computer to allow the user not to have to re-enter the user's password during visits to the Service. For the best experience the user is encouraged to enable/allow cookies.
  * Player.IO may compile users' data to produce statistics about the use of the Service. Such statistical information includes, but is not limited to, information showing the relative popularity of services and tools.
  * Player.IO shall not sell or share personal data with third parties. In the event that information is shared with third parties such information will not be personally identifiable information.
  * Users must be 13 years of age or older to use this service.
  * By accepting the Player.IO Terms of Use the user explicitly consents to use of personal data in accordance with this privacy policy. 
  * We store, process and/or transfer personal data to countries outside of the EEA, especially to servers in the US. We do this for the purposes of data management and legitimate business purposes described in the terms of service. If you do not agree to this procedure you should not use our services.
